hello.  In this video, I will show you how
anyone can easily create videos using free AI tools
.  In particular,
if you use Halio AI, you can generate
unlimited Easy2 image videos for a week
.
This video you are about to watch was also
created by me personally in just 10 minutes, from storyboarding to video production.
Today's content is a
beginner's guide for those new to AI video production
.  How do you like this video I made in just 20 minutes
?  I will
start now.  I am requesting Jaminai to create a storyboard for the story of the video made today
.  If
Jae-eun, who writes storyboards, doesn't have personal matters, I
will produce the video next Thursday or Friday.
First, let's check out the main character of today's video in the storyboard
.  The
main characters needed this time are Mom and Dad.
Now, let's create a character using Whisk
.  For example, please
enter "full body of a Korean male in his late 20s" and
continue generating until you get an image you like.  For the mom character, you
can do the same by entering "truth" as a full-body Korean woman in her late 20s and repeating the process until you get the desired result.
And please make sure to set the background to Studio
.  You must do this to
recognize the protagonist more accurately in the nano banana
.  Now, let's go into AI Studio and
run Nano Banana
.  First, attach the main character to the image and
copy the storyboard content you just created.  Then, I
can continue generating the scene I want until I get an image I like
.  Once the desired scene is complete,
please download the files and organize the names in order so that you do not get confused about the sequence later.  Now,
connect to Hilu AI.  Since the event period is one week, you
can create unlimited image videos.  To participate in the event,
log in with your Google account,
go to the Video category, and
create an image.  Making a video is
simple.  First,
combine the start and end images to
create a single video, and for the next video, use the
last image from the previous video
as the new start image. If
you continue this process until the end of the video, it will be
completed naturally.  To
use Hiluer, insert the start and end images
.  Enter
in English in the prompt how you want the video to look between the first and last frames
.  Disable the prompt camera option to get better results in the prompt
.
Select the Hiluer model, choose the video resolution and time for the
generated video gas, and then
press the generate button.  After waiting a moment,
download the desired video clip, and repeat the process until the entire video is created to
finish.
Now, return to the editing program,
edit the video, and once you finish editing, the
video will be complete.  Today, we looked at the process of completing a video
using free AI tools,
from storyboarding and character creation to video
production and a letter
.   We
plan to continue introducing AI video production methods that are easy for beginners to follow, so if you found this video helpful, please
subscribe and like.  I will be back
with more useful content in the next video
.