Are you still creating images manually one by one in Grok
?  We are
now releasing the Grok automation guide. With
just this method, you can easily produce large volumes of video and
even long-take footage
.  However, please watch carefully until the end, as
missing this important point introduced in the middle of the video may result in your X
account being suspended
.  We
plan to continue updating this kind of information, so please
subscribe and like.
Grok strictly prohibits the use of automatic tools
.
Since your account will be immediately suspended if you are caught using automated tools, we
recommend creating a new Google account to use Grok Automation.
Create a new account on Google,
log in to Chrome, and then
sign up for Grok.   In the
address bar at the top,
click the extensions icon, then go to Program Management,
click Web Store, and
search for Grok Automation.
Click Grok Automation at the top and
install the extension on Grom.
Click the Grom extension icon and
click the pin icon next to Grom Automation to pin it to the address bar
.
Enter Grok in Google Search and
log in to the Grok site.
Select an image from the left toolbar to
enter image video creation.
Click View site information in the address bar and change the site settings
popup redirection to Allow.
Now, let's go back to Grook and
try using Grook automation.
Clicking the Grok Automation icon at the top opens the side toolbar.   You
need to change a few settings;
select a frequently used aspect ratio and
determine the number of videos to create per prompt.  I recommend one, as doing multiple times may
cause problems
.
Change the maximum number of suggestions to 3 upon failure.  It seems that the
detection system in Grok activates if you generate 15 or more videos consecutively
.   For
automatic download upscale,
check if it is in upscale mode and if the language
is Korean, then press the save settings
icon below.   In the
case of text-to-video, it
creates a video by inputting text, while in the
case of frame-to-video, it generates an image by
uploading an image and then starting the image
.
Prompting is a very important
point.  It is a widely known fact that many
automation and Chrome extension developers in the Ready community have
conducted numerous tests, and if a
curb request is sent within 30 seconds, X's barrier
WF considers it a repair and disconnects the connection
. To avoid this, a delay of
30 to 60 seconds, similar to human breathing, is forcibly
implemented
.  I recommend 50 seconds
.
And for the video script, please
refer to the previously uploaded video.
This video is about
how to safely use the Chrome extension Grok, so I will
skip over this part.
Since we are creating a video by referencing an image, I will insert an image
.
Upload the images in order.
For reference, we recommend keeping the number of videos
to 15 or fewer.
When entering the prompt, exclude
all information such as the first and second gods,
leaving only the pure prompt.
And you can separate the first and second gods by
leaving a line blank
.  Now the image and prompt
connect, and the video duration of 6 seconds
is visible.  If you click here, you will see the connection feature. This
feature uses the last part of the current video as the first image of the next video, and
there are many changes to the character depending on the final scene.  Just keep in mind that this feature
exists.
Since an image has been included in every scene this time,
select 6 seconds and press the play button at the bottom
.  Now, do something else while
waiting for the video generation to finish
.  When the completion indicator appears in the prompt queue,
check if the file has been downloaded successfully.
If you open Pi Explorer, you
can confirm that the requested video has been downloaded successfully.
Grok AI delivers the
best results among free video creation programs
.  And Grok
Automation
is a very useful tool.  Therefore, you must
not have your account suspended or receive a hardware ban
.  I hope you make
sure to follow the final summary points from now on when using it
.  First delay time
section.  Set the interval between videos
to at least 30 to 60 times.
Second mass production orientation.
Instead of hanging hundreds at once,
work in batches of 5 to 15.
Third account monitoring.  If a temporary restriction
message appears, it is recommended to immediately stop the automation and
take a break for about half a day
. If you follow these three points, you
can use it safely
.  I hope today's content was helpful
.  thank you