Hello, this is Coco.
How can you tell if someone has blocked you on KakaoTalk?
To find the answer to this question, I have
prepared two mobile phones. One is
the phone to block, and the other is the phone to be blocked. I will
personally verify the effect of blocking on KakaoTalk using these two phones. To
block
someone on KakaoTalk, tap the three dots at the top right of their profile and
select "More." You will see that there are two types of blocking options:
blocking messages and blocking both messages and the profile.
Now, let's see
what happens when we block someone through a test.
For the first test, I
will block both messages and the profile. You can see that the
profile picture has disappeared from the profile icon, and the
KakaoPay icon has disappeared when you enter the profile.
For comparison, I will
try unblocking. The right side is
before blocking, and the left side is
after.
You can see that the profile and the KakaoPay icon have changed.
For the second test, I will block messages.
When messages are blocked, there is
no visible change in the profile picture or the KakaoPay icon in the profile information. To verify, I type a message in an existing chat room.
The message is not delivered to the phone that blocked messages. Next, let's
check the changes in a group chat room. The
participant information remains the
same as before, so it is impossible to confirm that a block has occurred.
So, I type a message.
Surprisingly, I can see that the message is delivered to the blocked phone.
Yes,
this time I will create a group chat room with three people, including myself. A
chat room with at least two people is necessary to verify that the chat room functions properly, provided
there is a non-blocked contact to send messages to.
To verify, I will
enter a message. In a normal case, I
can send the message to the person in the chat room immediately upon entering it. However, if they are blocked, I
cannot send messages, and you can
see that their profile is not displayed among the contacts. I will conclude the
test here and
summarize today's content. If
both messages and the profile are blocked,
when you check the other person's profile picture, the picture
disappears, and the KakaoPay icon vanishes from the profile information.
If only messages are blocked, you can send messages in the existing chat room,
open a new chat room, and
enter a message; if messages are blocked, you
cannot view the blocked profile. That is all. I
have shared information through actual testing on how blocking someone on KakaoTalk appears to them. If you liked today's content, please
subscribe and like.
I will update videos with information helpful for your daily life next time. This is IT
expert Hogu.