Are you still paying the full 29,000 won
every month for the paid version of Jemina all by yourself
? If you watch this video to the end, I will
show you how to fully use Google AI Jemina’s Oddvance for around 4,000 won, which is the price of a cup of coffee
.  If you
would like to continue receiving the latest information like this, please take a moment to
subscribe and like.   You
can share the Google AI program with up to six people, including family and friends
.  There is just one thing to note: the
main account and additional accounts must
all be created in the same country to be
usable.  In other words, the amount for the Moon Gu colleague
is 29,000 won, but if this is divided among six people, it
becomes 4,800 won per person.   It is
effective to receive an almost 80% discount.
After searching for Google Family Group on Google,
select the Google Family Group link from Google Family.  To communicate with a family group,
click the Start button and select Create Family Group
.  Now, if you press Confirm, this
account will become the main account of the family group
.  To add a configuration here,
enter five Google accounts and
click Send below.  Family group
creation is complete.
There is one additional task: you must verify that the added email
account is a valid Google account through an authentication process
.   If
you go to your additional account, you
can check that you have received an email to join the family group
.  Press the Accept Invitation button,
select Start in the invitation information, and then
press the Join Family button to complete the family group setup
.  If you finalize the remaining accounts like this,
six people can use it with one subscription.